Somewhere between Hollywood and the rest of the world.
Laurel Canyon is a drama, romance film directed by Lisa Cholodenko.
When an uptight young man and his fiancée move into his libertine mother's
house, the resulting clash of life attitudes shakes everyone up.
Jane, played by Frances McDormand.
Sam, played by Christian Bale.
Alex, played by Kate Beckinsale.
Sara, played by Natascha McElhone.
Ian McKnight, played by Alessandro Nivola.
Fripp, played by Lou Barlow.
Laurel Canyon is a 2002 American drama film written
and directed by Lisa Cholodenko.
The film stars Frances McDormand, Christian Bale, Kate
Beckinsale, Natascha McElhone, and Alessandro Nivola.
The film explores themes of single parent, pot smoking, los angeles,
california, threesome, older woman younger man relationship.
The tone is emotional.